{
    "subject": "resource/Randy_Quaid",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Texas",
    "human_readable": "Randy Quaid was born in Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9390877485275269,
            "question": "Where was Randy Quaid born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9248937964439392,
            "question": "Is Randy Quaid from Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7280942797660828,
            "question": "Randy Quaid's birthplace is known for what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.673647940158844,
            "question": "What state is associated with Randy Quaid's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45939359068870544,
            "question": "In which US state did Randy Quaid begin his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4108984172344208,
            "question": "Where did Randy Quaid's life begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.407225638628006,
            "question": "Texas is the birth state of which actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37717387080192566,
            "question": "Can you name a famous person born in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.318038672208786,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Randy Quaid's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22713743150234222,
            "question": "Which actor hails from Texas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Randy Quaid was born in Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7379_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Randy Quaid's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7379_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous person born in Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7379_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Texas is the birth state of which actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7379_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7379_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as all the files mention that Randy Quaid was born in Houston, Texas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Randy Quaid's birthplace, stating he was born in Houston, Texas. Therefore, the statement \"Randy Quaid was born in Texas\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}